

IVAN VILDE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER









ABOUT ME

I'm 26 years old front-end developer from Moscow. I had an experience of creating single-page application using react - redux-typescript, converting design to landing page.

Also i spend a lot of time with javascript, scss and graphic libraries.

I'm committed to selfdevelopment and learning new, that the main things why i enjoy coding.

SKILLS

- REACT / REDUX
- THUNK / SAGA
- HOOKS
- TYPESCRIPT
- JAVASCRIPT
- WEBSOCKET
- MATERIAL UI / BOOTSTRAP
- **REST API / AXIOS**
- UNIT TESTS / STORYBOOK
- HTML/CSS/SCSS
- GIT / GITHUB
- FORMIK

CONTACT DETAILS

Mobile Phone:

+79296372677

Email Address:

rendow33@gmail.com

City: Moscow

LANGUAGE

English intermediate in progress

WORK EXPERIENCE

LLC "TRANSCONVERTER"

Technical Service Engineer | 2019 - May 2019

Diagnostics, computer diagnostics and repair of Siemens high-voltage converters. Work with Siemens software.

LLC "ARSENAL-CLIMATE"

Technical Service Engineer | 2018 - April 2019

Service and repair of refrigeration and compressor equipment. Software setting of air conditioning equipment.

EDUCATIONS

MOSCOW COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY

Installation and technical operation of refrigeration and compressor equipment

IT-INCUBATOR.BY

Front-end developer. React, Redux, TypeScript | 2020 - 2021

ENGLISH COURSES

SkillSet | 2020